<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaizhao Sun</title>
    <link>https://ksun46.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kaizhao Sun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ksun46.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A stochastic process crib sheet</title>
      <link>https://ksun46.github.io/posts/stochref/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksun46.github.io/posts/stochref/</guid>
      <description>A one-page crib sheet for stochastic process is attached here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://ksun46.github.io/1_about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksun46.github.io/1_about/</guid>
      <description>Short Bio I am a Ph.D. candidate in Operations Research at Georgia Tech, working with Dr. Andy Sun. I am interested in the theory and application of optimization in a broad sense. I am currently working on distributed and decomposition algorithms for nonconvex optimization, which find their applications in large-scale continuous and discrete problems arising from engineering, especially power systems, and data science.
Before joining the Ph.D. program, I received my B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://ksun46.github.io/3_experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksun46.github.io/3_experience/</guid>
      <description>Grid Optimization Competition I have been participating in the ARPA-E Grid Optimization Competition (GO Competition). Entrant teams from around the globe thrive to develop innovative algorithmic softwares for modern power grids in the form of coding competition. Our team (GMI-GO) is led by faculty advisors Prof. X. Andy Sun (PI) and Prof. Santanu Dey, and it has been a pleasure for me working with and learning from wonderful teammates Amin Gholami and Shixuan Zhang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misc</title>
      <link>https://ksun46.github.io/4_misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksun46.github.io/4_misc/</guid>
      <description>Invited and Contributed Talks  Algorithms for DC Programs Based on DME Smoothing  SIAM Conference on Optimization, Virtual, July 2021 INFORMS Annual Meeting, Anaheim, CA, USA, October 2021   Decomposition Methods for Global Solutions of Mixed-Integer Linear Programs  Integer Programming and Combinatorial Optimization (IPCO) Workshop (poster), Virtual, May 2021 Mixed Integer Programming (MIP) Workshop (poster), Virtual, May 2021   A Two-level ADMM Algorithm for AC OPF with Global Convergence Guarantee  Power Systems Engineering Research Center (PSERC) Meeting (poster)  Phoenix, AZ, USA, December 2017 Wichita, KS, USA, May 2018,   Georgia Tech Workshop on Electric Energy Systems and Optimization (poster)  Atlanta, GA, USA, November 2018 Atlanta, GA, USA, November 2019   INFORMS Annual Meeting, Virtual, October 2020   Distributed Algorithms for Sparse Regression  INFORMS Annual Meeting, Seattle, WA, USA, October 2019   A Two-level Distributed Algorithm for Nonconvex Constrained Optimization  INFORMS Annual Meeting, Phoenix, AZ, USA, October 2018 International Conference on Continuous Optimization (ICCOPT), Berlin, Germany, August 2019    Academic Services  Co-chair of the session Distributed and Decentralized Optimization, ICCOPT 2019, Berlin, Germany Reviewer for MPC, JOTA, IEEE (TAC, TCNS, TII, TPWRS, TSG), ACC, CDC, IET, Quantum  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://ksun46.github.io/2_research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksun46.github.io/2_research/</guid>
      <description>Research Interest Topics of recent interests:
 Distributed and decomposition algorithms for continuous/discrete optimization Theory and algorithms based on nonconvex augmented Lagrangian duality Convexification and smoothing in optimization Sampling algorithms  Publication and Preprint  Log-difference-of-convex (Log-DC) sampling by the unadjusted Langevin Algorithm  Jiaming Liang* , Kaizhao Sun, Enlu Zhou, and Andy Sun Submitted, 2021   Solving large-scale security-constrained optimal power flow problems  Amin Gholami, Kaizhao Sun, Shixuan Zhang* , and Andy Sun Submitted, 2021   Algorithms for DC programs based on difference-of-Moreau-envelopes smoothing  Kaizhao Sun and Andy Sun Submitted, 2021   Decomposition methods for global solutions of mixed-integer linear programs  Kaizhao Sun, Mou Sun, and Wotao Yin Submitted, 2021   A two-level ADMM algorithm for AC OPF with global convergence guarantees  Kaizhao Sun and Andy Sun Accepted at IEEE Transactions on Power Systems, 2021   A two-level distributed algorithm for nonconvex constrained optimization  Kaizhao Sun and Andy Sun Submitted, 2019    * Optimization experts currently on the academic job market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>