<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kaizhao Sun</title>
    <link>https://ksun46.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kaizhao Sun</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ksun46.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A stochastic process crib sheet</title>
      <link>https://ksun46.github.io/posts/stochref/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksun46.github.io/posts/stochref/</guid>
      <description>A one-page crib sheet for stochastic process is attached here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>https://ksun46.github.io/3_experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksun46.github.io/3_experience/</guid>
      <description>Past Experiences  Georgia Tech, Atlanta, GA, USA, August 2017 - May 2022  Graduate research and teaching assistant   Decision Intelligence Lab, DAMO Academy, Alibaba Group US, Bellevue, WA, USA, Summer 2020  Research intern    Grid Optimization Competition I have participated in the ARPA-E Grid Optimization Competition (GO Competition). Entrant teams from around the globe strive to develop innovative algorithmic software for modern power grids in the form of coding competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Misc</title>
      <link>https://ksun46.github.io/4_misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksun46.github.io/4_misc/</guid>
      <description>Awards and Honors  Prize-winning team in ARPA-E Grid Optimization Challenge 2, Oct. 2021 Third-place team in ARPA-E Grid Optimization Challenge 1, Feb. 2020 McLean Fellowship Stipend, Fall 2018 and Spring 2019 ISyE Stipend, Fall 2017 and Spring 2018  Invited and Contributed Talks  Dual Descent ALM and ADMM  ISyE Ph.D. Student Seminar, GA, USA, Nov. 2021 INFORMS Annual Meeting, Indianapolis, IN, Oct. 2022   Algorithms for DC Programs Based on DME Smoothing  SIAM Conference on Optimization, Virtual, Jul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://ksun46.github.io/2_research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ksun46.github.io/2_research/</guid>
      <description>Research Interest Topics of recent interests:
 Distributed and decomposition algorithms for continuous/discrete optimization Theory and algorithms based on nonconvex augmented Lagrangian duality Convexification and smoothing in optimization  Publications [Google Scholar] Preprints  Recent Developments in Security-Constrained AC Optimal Power Flow: Overview of Challenge 1 in the ARPA-E Grid Optimization Competition  Ignacio Aravena, Daniel K Molzahn, Shixuan Zhang, et al. Submitted, 2022   Dual descent ALM and ADMM  Kaizhao Sun and Andy Sun Submitted, 2021   Decomposition Methods for Global Solutions of Mixed-Integer Linear Programs  Kaizhao Sun, Mou Sun, and Wotao Yin Submitted, 2022   Log-Difference-of-Convex (Log-DC) Sampling by the Unadjusted Langevin Algorithm  Jiaming Liang, Kaizhao Sun, Enlu Zhou, and Andy Sun    Refereed Papers   Amin Gholami, Kaizhao Sun, Shixuan Zhang, and Andy Sun.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>